他们都会来
They're all coming.
室内围巾  全木纹  爱神
Scarves Indoors, Wood grain on Everything, Love God.
你可能在那个网络神片里见过他
You've probably seen him in that viral video.
准备好感受今晚的爱了吗
Who's ready for love tonight?
希望没人拍
I hope nobody's filming this.
喔  是那种真正的演唱会式的音乐节吗
Whoa, like a real concert concert?
我还  我还从来没去过这样的音乐节呢
I've-- I've never actually been to one of those before.
那是因为你从来没有找到一群志同道合的小伙伴陪你一起去
That's because you've never had an awesome crew to roll with before.
快点啊  汤普森
Come on, Thompson.
舔那块海绵  舔那块海绵
Lick that sponge. Lick that sponge.
噢  我简直不敢相信他真的这么做了
Oh! I can't believe he's doing it.
他在干什么啊
What is he doing?
我们带你一起玩
When you're with us, you're in.